http://www.ic0nstrux.com/privacy-policy

Currency:$£€  | Account LoginShopping Cart 0 item(s) - $0.00 HomeProductsVideoTutorialsSupportForumBlogAboutContactLatestPropeller Project Board USB $24.95
CategoriesGaming SystemsRoboticsDevelopment KitsMicrocontroller ModulesFPGA/CPLD KitsArduino/CompatiblesAdd-On BoardsLCD/OLED/CRTData/Storage/MemoryPeripherals/Human Input DevicesPower/Solar/BatteriesSensorsSound/AudioWireless Technology Programmers/DebugElectronic Parts/ICsPrototypingTest Equipment/GearTools/FabricationBooks
ManufacturersAtmelLattice SemiconductorMicrochipNurve NetworksParallaxTrossen Robotics Resources Cool LinksLink ExchangeAdvertise With UsContracts/ContractorsSell Ur Stuff!!!AccountLogin / RegisterForgot PasswordMy AccountWish ListOrder HistoryDownloadsReturnsTransactionsNewsletterSponsored SitesHome » Privacy PolicyPrivacy PolicyNurve Networks LLC has created this statement to demonstrate our commitment to privacy. The following statement discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this web site.Information Automatically Logged We log visitor IP addresses for usage tracking, server problem diagnosis, and general website maintenance. Cookies Our site uses cookies to track information about our visitors and to help serve them better.Order Forms Our site provides order forms for you to buy products. When you place an order with us, we collect contact information such as email, mailing addresses and financial information such as credit card numbers. Contact information from the order forms is used only for orders, shipping and contest winner notification and newsletters. This includes sending you the product(s) you ordered and contacting you if there's a problem with your order. Financial information that is collected is used to bill you for the order.External Links This site contains links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or the nature of the content of said sites.Public Forums In the future, this site may contain chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or newsgroups available to its visitors. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information, so you should exercise caution should you decide to disclose your personal information.Security This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. This site provides a secure server for all credit card orders, securely encrypting all personal data with industry-standard methods.InformationAboutSupportContactSite MapCustomer ServiceCool LinksLink ExchangeAdvertise With UsContracts/ContractorsCustomer ServicePrivacy PolicyTerms & ConditionsDelivery InformationMy AccountMy AccountNewsFollow us on:We accept: Powered by Nurve Networks LLC ©2013-2020
